http://www.projectgraphics.com/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeWhat We DoCompany ProfileCase StudiesProductsBrand Marketing ProductsOutdoor PromotionsLight Pole BannerTrade Shows and CeremoniesCommercial Holiday DecorationsVenues We ServeCampus EnvironmentsCommunities & StreetscapesBeverages & RestaurantsRetail & Shopping DestinationsPoint of SaleBlog Connect With UsCatalogStoreVote & Census BannersLight Pole BannersHoliday Light Pole BannersSpring Design Light Pole BannersPurple SpringHalf Sun SpringGreen SpringBlue SpringBeach Shells Yellow SummerGreen w/ Purple Flowers SpringHistorical DisplaysPop-Up Tents & AccessoriesTablecoversBlade and Teardrop Banners8ft. Blade Banners11ft Blade Banners16ft. Blade Banners7ft Teardrop Banners11ft. Teardrop Banners16ft. Teardrop BannersCrowd Barrier Covers Crownline ProductsPPE (Personal Protection Equipment)Virus Prevention Graphics for Customer ConfidenceCart File TransferPrivacy Policy:Project Graphics ("Project Graphics")
operates Projectgraphics.com and may operate other websites. It
is Project Graphics's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, Project Graphics collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Project Graphics's purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how Project Graphics's visitors use its website. From time to
time, Project Graphics may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.Project Graphics also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on Projectgraphics.com
blogs/sites. Project Graphics only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to Project Graphics's websites choose to interact
with Project Graphics in ways that require Project Graphics to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Project Graphics gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at Projectgraphics.com to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Project Graphics are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, Project Graphics collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
Project Graphics. Project Graphics does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsProject Graphics may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. Project Graphics may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, Project Graphics does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationProject Graphics discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on Project Graphics's behalf or to provide services available
at Project Graphics's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using Project Graphics's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. Project Graphics will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, Project Graphics discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when Project Graphics believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of Project Graphics, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an Project Graphics website and have supplied your email address, Project Graphics
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with Project Graphics and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Project Graphics takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Project Graphics uses cookies to
help Project Graphics identify and track visitors, their usage of Project Graphics
website, and their website access preferences. Project Graphics visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using Project Graphics's websites, with the drawback that certain features
of Project Graphics's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf Project Graphics, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that Project Graphics goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of Project Graphics may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by Project Graphics and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, Project Graphics may change
its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Project Graphics's sole
discretion. Project Graphics encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Privacy Policy. If you have a Projectgraphics.com account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
